# BOLARI, **ANGELIKI**

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

Work experience in Supply Chain, Logistics, Accounting and Sales. Demonstrated capability to work at a fast-pace projectized environment, capable of working alone or as part of a team. Open to critique for improvement, fast learner, detailoriented prone to a lean philosophy. Known for creative thinking.

Recently I decided to fully commit to pursuing a career in Software development Machine and Learning combining self-studies with an MSc, while working on real life projects.

### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Python, Django, SQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap **Data Cleaning and Data Analysis** Deep Learning (Machine Vision & NLP)

#### **Project Management**

Planning, Adaptability, Decision Making, Time Management, **Continuous Improvement** 

> Greek (Native) English (Advanced) Japanese (Intermediate)

# CONTACT DETAILS

C: 00306973203410 E: angeliki.bolari@gmail.com L: www.linkedin.com/in/angeliki-G: https://github.com/AngBol A: Thessaloniki, 54655, Greece

### **WORK HISTORY**

# **Logistics and Supply Chain Coordinator**

KALLIMARMARON | Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2018

Created **Demand Planning**, Managed Supplies and procurement of consumables, Directed annual and semiannual inventory check, Managed transportation operations, Handled 3rd party assets life-cycle.

# Financial Operator

KALLIMARMARON | Dec.2011-Mar.2014

Managed cash flow, payable accounts, accounting records and financial data, delivered insights and reports leading to decision-making by the management team

more information on the back.

# ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

### **AUTh - School of Informatics**

MSc Digital Media - Computational Intelligence | 2019-

### T.E.I. of Central Macedonia - Informatics Engineering

BSc Informatics and Communication Engineering | 2005-2011

# **SELF EDUCATION**

Deep Learning Specialization - Deeplearning.ai Python for Everybody Specialization - University of Michigan Machine Learning - Stanford University

Web Design for Everybody Specialization - University of Michigan

Supply Chain Principles - Georgia Institute of Technology, Excel Skills for **Business Specialization** - Macquarie University, Introduction to **Project Management Principles and Practices** Specialization - University of California, Irvine,

# **DETAILED WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Logistics and Supply Chain Coordinator | Mar.2014-Aug.2018

Operated on different levels of the company's supply chain:

- Created Demand Planning of consumables for manufacturing, balanced stock levels to satisfy manufacturing process requirements
- Managed Supplies and procurement of consumables (Production machinery and Office). Interacted
  with suppliers for pricing and delivery, evaluated responses, issued PO and monitored progress up to
  delivery. Ensured on-time deliveries, verified receipt and invoice charges
- Directed annual and semiannual inventory check of raw materials, consumables and finished stored products of the company's 16.000 m2 production facilities and warehouse covering over 950 active product codes, managed to cut processing time by 30%
- Managed transportation operations for inbound and outbound logistics on open orders up to their completion for both domestic and international projects
- Handled 3rd party assets in the company's facilities for safekeeping or manufacturing/processing, issuing service invoices and outbound transportation documents

#### Financial Operator | Dec.2011-Mar.2014

- Keeping track of Budget and Funds in order to manage cash flow in an efficient manner
- Created and maintained forms managing payable accounts of all branch employees, monitoring absence/presence and overtime
- Daily updating of the general ledger, providing reliable accounting records and financial data to the operations management for decision-making, ensuring that all accounting and control procedures are in order
- Produced monthly and annual reports and presentations of financial data to stakeholders
- Responsible for monthly and year-end closing procedures, making journal entry adjustments as necessary

#### Administrative Support | Nov.2010-Dec.2011

- Trained colleagues in the company's ERP and CRM programs optimizing company operations and customer relations
- · Liaised with consulting company for Implementation of ISO and CE certificates
- Assisting with applicants' and newly hired employees' paperwork and processes
- Preparing and maintaining confidential documents and information
- Monthly meetings with the company's safety technician to ensure all safety measures are in order in the production facilities
- Managing business trips for staff and controlling all relevant expenses
- · Acting as point of contact for all kinds of inquiries, both internal and external
- Handling and resolving customer complaints, developing solutions to multiple issues
- Many years of tradeshow experience (domestic and international)